The light awakens.
This Omega Area,
our sacred place will be
brought to destruction by the light.
Other lights can be seen.
Lights of the stars.
The luster of the Guardian Stars.
Our old world...
This Omega Area is
full of the power similar to ours.
Everyone gravitates to
that great aura.
In the luster of Guardian Stars,
I sense a light similar to
Taioron Crystal, the spring of our power.
I'm fascinated...
But this sacred place is ours.
We shall create a new world here!
I'll never let anyone get in my way.
Delete any foreign substances!
I know, sir.
Master Pharaoh 90.
The light brings us
to destruction.
Never let it awaken.
Wake up.
The time has come.
The light guided by the three Talismans.
The beginning of doom.
Fall in love, girls
Koi seyo otome
A flower's life is short and beautiful
hana no inochi wa hakanaku utsukushii
I shall cast a spell
so you can become who you want to be
naritai mono ni nareru mahou
kakete ageru
Your eyes show anxiety
yureru sono manazashi
The vision showed by mild fever
binetsu ga miseru maboroshi wa
It's a perfect world that makes me sad
kanashii hodo ni kanpeki na sekai
I can't laugh it off
waraenai yo
Something will happen tonight
The Premonition knocks on the door
konya nanika ga okiru
yokan ga tobira wo tataku
The moon light is gone
tsukiakari ga kiete
The beginning of the parade is
the new moon
parade no hajimari wa new moon
The future in the shining universe
sparks and turns into meteor shower
kirakira hikaru sora niwa future
mekurumeite ryuuseigun
My excitement is being fulfilled
I'm caught by your force of attraction
tokimeki michite iku
kimi no inryoku ni kizuite shimatta
The beginning is the new moon
hajimari wa new moon
Act.27 INFINITY 1
Premonition - First Part
What was that?
What was that dream?
What's that?
What was that vision of fire?
Somehow it's too bright...
What is that light?
The sound of bells?
Maybe this is...
...the sound of bells for
the wedding of Mamo-chan and I?
Usagi, it's past 8.
Why didn't you wake me earlier?
I wonder why she never learns?
You're right, Ikuko Mama.
Usagi is a perpetual child.
Continuing with the news.
An unidentified monster appeared
in a park in Minato Ward.
"Reversion?
Unidentified monster emerges"
Girls around there from the Private
Mugen Academy were attacked.
It was a bizarre incident.
According to a witness,
a girl from the same school...
...suddenly morphed into a monster.
Officials suggest
it's a case of reversion.
What's reversion, Kenji Papa?
Our human ancestors
once resembled gorillas.
Reversion is returning
to such a state.
But I wonder
if it really was a monster?
Reversion?
A human changes into a monster?
I'm off to school.
I have to go, too.
I'm leaving, Kenji Papa.
Yeah. Take care.
I'm so sorry, Mamo-chan.
You're late, Usa.
I was about to leave without you.
Mamo-chan, my dear.
Sorry to be late.
From tomorrow,
I'll make sure I'm never late again.
So please give me
a good morning kiss.
Good morning, Mamo-chan.
I'm steamed!
Good morning, Mamoru-sama.
Hi, Diana.
Good morning to you, too.
Oh, I forgot.
Usagi, you left your lunch at home.
You'd better get up earlier
and have breakfast.
Breakfast is the lifeblood
for your day.
Well said, Chibi-Usa.
She's getting carried away.
Such a sassy girl!
Actually, she's from the future.
The daughter of Mamo-chan and I.
She came to the past from the 30th century
to be trained as a Sailor Guardian.
She's staying at my home.
Hello, Chibi-Usa-chan.
Here's Momo-chan and her friend.
I'm off.
A memory of the fierce battle with the
Black Moon for the future of Earth...
...has faded into a dream.
I, Usagi Tsukino, and my associations
are leading a peaceful life.
Wake up.
The beginning of doom.
Mamo-chan?
No.
It's nothing.
The next moment I feel happiness,
an anxiety flashes in my mind.
I have a feeling my
current happiness won't last long.
Oh, well.
That's my fate.
I shall overcome whatever happens.
If that's what I must suffer
to fulfill my mission.
Kaiohmaru?
Good morning.
It's time to pick him up.
Or we'll be late for school.
The sea will be rough today.
Haruka! You applied full power
when you went down the straight.
This machine is awesome.
I wanted to go faster.
You shouldn't.
Not during the test phase.
I said not to exceed 5000 rpm.
You'll damage the car.
He's so popular.
Don't you know him?
That's Haruka Tenoh.
He is a gifted young driver that Japan
can be proud of after a long interval.
Those choppers, Tenohmaru and Kaiohmaru,
belong to Haruka and his girlfriend.
They use them to go to school.
What a life!
Hello, Michiru?
You're late.
It's a strong wind today.
Look.
That's Michiru Kaioh, the violinist.
So she's really dating Haruka?
I'm in shock.
I hate to admit,
but they're a perfect couple.
They go to the same school, too.
It's much-talked-about.
Yes, that Mugen Academy.
It's here.
Good day, Motoki-san.
Welcome, Usagi-chan and Naru-chan.
You're late.
I finished reading a book while
I was waiting for you, Usagi-chan.
That's Ami Mizuno.
A kind-hearted genius girl
with an IQ of 300.
I thought you'd be
the last here anyway, Usagi.
You're so mean, Rei-chan!
This cool beauty's name is Rei Hino.
A shrine maiden with a
strong spiritual power.
We've been waiting for you, Usagi.
That's Minako Aino.
She had fought as a Sailor V-chan
before we awakened as Sailor Guardians.
Over here, hurry.
This game is awesome.
That's Makoto Kino,
a strong girl with many loves.
She loves plants and is a gifted chef.
We're Sailor Guardians bonded by
fate from our previous lives.
If all five of us are together,
we can overcome any problems.
"Battle Lap?"
A game where we race together?
Yes, you can experience
a real race.
Wear your helmet.
Step on the clutch
and start the engine.
Listen to that engine!
Very realistic.
Keep changing up
till you get to the 5th gear.
It's like driving a real car.
Scary!
Step hard on the gas pedal
and rev up.
Who are you?
Fantastic!
It took barely a moment
to recover 1 lap behind.
Check out his time.
He drives like
a professional racer.
How fast is he going?
400 km/h!?
Usagi, that's far too dangerous.
What?
Are you okay?
The damage from the crash
felt so real.
You were really fast, Usagi.
With the helmet on,
it didn't feel that fast at all.
Really?
If that's what you think,
you have a talent for racing.
Excuse me.
You...
The color of your eyes is so noble.
Maybe a prince
in your previous life?
How can you say such a thing?
It's a mirror
that reflects previous lives.
Okay then.
Let's you and I race.
Bye, Bun-head.
He's so cool!
Sorry for saying such an odd thing.
Don't let it bother you.
Goodbye.
You became so close to her.
Are you jealous?
No way.
That Bun-head girl is cute,
still like a child.
Here it comes.
That long-absent sensation
of love approaching.
Hey, Usagi.
I bet that cool guy is somehow famous.
I've seen him somewhere before.
His school uniform...
That's it.
He's a student at Mugen Academy.
That Mugen Academy?
Mugen Academy?
Don't tell me you don't know.
Sankakusu, the biggest commercial area of
all the reclamation projects in Tokyo Bay.
It's a new private school
in Mugen District in that precinct.
When are you here, Umino?
It's full of gifted students, including
show biz stars and Olympic athletes.
Famous musicians
and many others.
Everyone's talking about it.
It's like "the academy of geniuses."
You're very well-informed, Minako-chan.
Some of the current
biggest stars are pupils there.
They have a massive hall
even available for concerts.
You could meet stars
only if you go to that school.
I wish I could transfer to it.
She's such a fangirl.
"The academy of geniuses" means
Usagi has no connection with.
You cut me!
You're too honest, Rei-chan.
And you delivered a final blow.
Ami-chan...
Hey look.
"16 year-old gifted racer, Haruka Tenoh"
I thought I'd seen him
somewhere before.
He's the professional race car driver,
Haruka Tenoh.
Really?
So he's an actual racer?
That's why he's such a good driver.
Does he hang around Juban Mall?
Maybe we can see him again.
Look. They're students
from Mugen Academy.
Their girl's uniform is so pretty.
It sure is!
I'll take care of Naru-chan and Umino.
You handle the monster.
Okay, Mamo-chan.
Guys, let's transform.
Okay!
Moon Cosmic Power
Make Up!
Mercury Planet Power
Mars Planet Power
Make Up!
Jupiter Planet Power
Venus Planet Power
Make Up!
The Pretty Guardian in a Sailor Suit,
Guardian of Love and Justice.
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Protected by Mercury, the Planet of Water.
Guardian of Wisdom.
Sailor Mercury!
Douse yourself in water and repent!
Protected by Mars, the Planet of Fire.
Guardian of War.
Sailor Mars!
In the name of Mars,
I will chastise you!
Protected by Jupiter, the Planet of
Thunder. Guardian of Protection.
Sailor Jupiter!
I'll make you feel so much regret,
it'll leave you numb!
Protected by Venus, Planet of Beauty.
Guardian of Love.
Sailor Venus!
Allow me to punish you with love!
What's that?
Reversion?
I see a girl ingested in the monster.
I will remove the evil spirit.
Evil Spirit, be exorcized!
Leave it to us.
Jupiter?
Okay.
Venus...
...Wink Chain Sword!
Jupiter Coconut...
...Cyclone!
What was that?
Call an ambulance!
Quickly.
Sure!
I feel like being watched.
Any Enemies left?
Venus?
No, it's nothing.
The moment she transformed
into a monster, my brooch reacted.
The "Legendary Silver Crystal" reacted.
These are...
Reversions.
No mistake.
You all watched the morning news,
did you?
About that girl turning into a monster
and attacking people.
She's also a student
at Mugen Academy.
A new enemy?
Mugen Academy and reversions...
That sounds very suspicious.
Now we have to go and investigate
Mugen Academy.
Sure.
Let's go.
To Mugen Academy.
Jumping over thousands of dawns
Jumping over eternity
Ikusen no yoake wo tobikoete
Eien mo tobikoete
Every time I divine through the mirror
kagami no mukou uranau tabi ni
The shining truth is the only one
hikari hanatsu shinjitsu wa hitotsu
At the edge of the universe
with my frosty sword
kono sora no hate kooru yaiba de
I will tear the veil of night
yoru no tobari mo kirisaite iku
Buzzing of my heart are
like the endless sound of the surf
nariyamanu shiosai no youna
mune no zawameki ga
Becoming the first wind of spring
haru wo tsugeru kaze ni nari
It catches us and surpasses us
bokura wo oikosunda
We repeat thousands of eternities
ikusen no eien wo kurikaesu
In the boundless, lonely darkness
hateshinai kodoku no yami no naka de
I've been looking for you
anata wo sagashiteta
All my life
zutto sagashiteita
As I've been led by force of attraction
inryoku ni michibikareru mama
motsureta akai ito wo hodoku youni
Like untangling our red threads
ryuusei ni notte aini yuku kara
I'll come to see you
riding on a shooting star
toki wo koe haruka
Over time, far off
sadame ga michiru
Fate is fulfilled
sono shunkan wo ima tomo ni futari de
Now we share the fateful moment
That's a reversion!
I, Sailor Moon will never forgive villains
who disturb love and peace!
Next episode Act. 27 INFINITY 1
Premonition - The 2nd part.
The Moonlight is the Message of Love.